Luciana Chamorro Full Stack Developer

• Buenos Aires, Argentina

• <u>lucianachamorro87@gmail.com</u>

Linkedin

•Github

In Full Stack Development I discovered the perfect mix of what I am passionate about: tech and solving problems. I am experienced working with NodeJS, React, Redux, SQL as well as other technologies in the industry. Self-taught by nature I have creative thinking, enjoy teamwork, good communication skills, and autonomy.

Technologies

HTML, CSS, Javascript, React, Redux, Node.js, Express, Postgres, Sequelize, Scrum and agile methodologies.

Proyectos

Full Stack Web Developer - Marvel App

Henry Bootcamp, Buenos Aires, Argentina.

May. 22 - May. 22

- Develop and design React SPA that consumes Marvel Comics API. The purpose of the app was to offer the customer/visitor access to the catalog of comics and characters, and purchase a subscription for reading access.
- Plan and develop in frontend and collaborate with the backend generating the routes required to assemble the components in question and implement complementary technologies.
- Solve contingencies and plan to achieve the stipulated deadlines.
- Implement technologies such as React, Redux, CSS and libraries (Semantic UI, Material UI), Auth0, payment gateway with Paypal, backend developed in Node.js with Express. Database in PostgreSQL and Sequelize.

Link al repo

Full Stack Web Developer - PokemonApp

Henry Bootcamp, Buenos Aires, Argentina.

Apr. 22 - Apr. 22

- Design and development of a pokemon SPA that includes: searches, filters, sorting and creation of new pokemons for later query in the database.
- Build the app using for the frontend: React Js, Redux, pure CSS and the backend was developed in Node.js/ Express. Database with PostgreSQL and Sequelize.

Link al repo

Education

HENRY BOOTCAMPFull Stack Web Developer.

Remote

Jan 2022 – May 2022

- + 700 hours of theoretical-practical intensive coursework. 2022.
- ==> Extra class activity: As part of the Bootcamp, as 'Henry Hero', I've collaborated answering questions from new students via slack and live streaming solving exercises/homeworks of prep courses.

NATIONAL UNIVERSITY QUILMES

Biotechnology Degree

Argentina

[Promedio: 8.26, in progress]

CACIPRA INSTITUTE Argentina

Luciana Chamorro Full Stack Developer

Experience

SELF EMPLOYED

BsAs, Argentina

Insurance Professional agent Mat SSN 94363

Jul 2018 –Present

- Collaborate with individuals and companies in the design of life and retirement policies for the protection of family and assets.
- Manage in property insurance field and supply the appropriate contracts for each need, for individuals and industry.

METLIFE SA Argentina

Professional agent

Ago 2015 – Jul 2018

- Provide comprehensive advice on life, accident and home insurance.
- Achieve monthly business objectives and quality metrics.

ZURICH ARGENTINA SA

Argentina

Professional agent

Nov 2011 – Jul 2015

- Provide comprehensive automotor insurance advice, underwriting and follow-up.
- Achieve monthly business objectives and quality metrics...

Leadership & Activities

HARVARD CS50

Remote

• Cs50 Introduction to Computer Science

Skills & Interests

Technologies: HTML, CSS, Javascript, React, Redux, Node is, Express, Postgres, Sequelize.

Language: Inglés - CLFR = C

Laboratory: Analytical and testing techniques in general, and in particular those related to tissue culture, recombinant

DNA techniques (blotting, PCR, etc.), as well as safety measures and keep of good practices..

Interests: Reading, cooking, movies.